<archimate:ArchimateModel
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Open Government of Canada Architecture Git Repository"
    id="1f0d7762-0011-48d2-a572-f535f1e5a423"
    purpose="# Open Government of Canada Architecture Git Repository&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The canada-ca/architecture repository is meant for the storage of architecture models for use within and about the Government of Canada. The contents of this repository are provided without any warranty or guarentee, and does not necisarily accurately reflect the Government of Canada's current state of Enterprise Architecture management at any given moment.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;In line with [Open Government](https://open.canada.ca) principles, this repository supports open government. &quot;Open Government is about making government more accessible to everyone. This means giving greater access to government data and information to the Canadian public and the businesses community.[About Open Government](https://open.canada.ca/en/about-open-government).&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;This repository is governed using an informal, community driven governance model.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;## What you will find here&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;This repository will contain elements created from open and accessible information and data sources such as:&#xD;&#xA;* Legislation&#xD;&#xA;* Acts&#xD;&#xA;* Regulations&#xD;&#xA;* Policies&#xD;&#xA;* Directives&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;## What you wont find here&#xD;&#xA;This repository is not mean to expose non-public or protected information sources such as:&#xD;&#xA;* Internal business transformation&#xD;&#xA;* Internal departmental policies&#xD;&#xA;* personal or self-identifiable information&#xD;&#xA;* any information presenting exposing security threats or internal network topologies&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;## About Enterprise Architecture within Government of Canada&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Enterprise Architecture in its current form within the Government of Canada is heavily focused on the Management of IM/IT, however its principles can be found across all viewpoints of the organization within the Architecture Development Model (ADM) including Business, Information and systems, as well as technology.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The [Government of Canada Strategic Plan for Information Management and Information Technology 2017 to 2021](https://www.canada.ca/en/treasury-board-secretariat/services/information-technology/strategic-plan-2017-2021.html#toc8-2-2) states, &quot;Sound IM-IT management starts with consistent planning based on documented descriptions of the enterprise. With an understanding of what is in play, managers can adopt solutions that best address their business needs while advancing government-wide architecture.&quot;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;[Directive on Management of Information Technology](https://www.tbs-sct.gc.ca/pol/doc-eng.aspx?id=15249), provides guidance on how to assess Enterprise Architecture through Appendix C - Mandatory Procedures for Enterprise Architecture Assessment."
    version="4.4.0">
  <properties
      key="URL"
      value="https://github.com/canada-ca/architecture"/>
  <properties/>
  <metadata/>
</archimate:ArchimateModel>
